{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209521460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209521460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209544207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209544206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuogelea_kuonyesha_kuwavutia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209550850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209550850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kuvuta_kumwoa_kuvuta_kumpiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209557445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209557444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kuanguka_kununua_kuanguka_kuolewa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209564088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209564088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kuimba_kumpiga_kuonekana_kuimba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209570725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209570725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kumpikia_kuuza_kufanya_kumpikia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209577370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209577370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kukimbia_kukimbia_kumfanya_kufika"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209583987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209583987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kucheka_kutoa_kuanguka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209590608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209590608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kuvuka_kuna_kuvuka_kumwambia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209597210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209597210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kuangalia_kuangalia_kusoma_kujificha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209604664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209604663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kuangalia_kuangalia_kusoma_kujificha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209613653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209613652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kuangalia_kuangalia_kusoma_kujificha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209619411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209619411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3714c099-ab99-4a6a-89e3-6a21fec74fb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ku.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kuangalia_kuangalia_kusoma_kujificha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209648401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209648401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209650526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209650526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209658884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209658884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209661645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209661645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209670384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209670384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209671905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209671905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209681081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209681081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209683196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209683191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209692485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209692485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209694155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209694155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209702797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209702797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209712728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209712728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209721160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209721160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209723908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209723908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209734443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209734443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209735951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209735951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209745508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209745508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209748356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209748356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209758777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209758777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209762156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209762156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209772519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209772519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209778364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209778364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209784943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209784943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209786993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209786993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209798075","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209798074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209805741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209805741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3254fa46-8c85-4d57-ac8f-edeec4ee6266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ku.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ku__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209814858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209814857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209817970","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209817970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209820878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209820878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209823836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209823835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209827033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209827033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" NAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209830010","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209830010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209832489","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209832489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209835481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209835481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209838389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209838389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nami"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209841348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209841348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NARO"," userResponse":" NARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209844749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209844749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209844820","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209844819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NARO"," userResponse":" NARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209876262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209876262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f4fe679c-b926-462f-8d43-7f72f0269355"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209891294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209891294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nazo_tatu-nazo-gogo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nazo"," userResponse":" nazo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209901703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209901703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_kisu-nasi-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209910293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209910293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-bado-zuri"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209919982","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209919982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naro_naro-wenu-haja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naro"," userResponse":" naro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209929662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209929661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naro_goti-miti-naro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naro"," userResponse":" naro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209938921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209938921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_ziwe-hiyo-nalo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209956651","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209956651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nanu_soko-kuwa-nanu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nanu"," userResponse":" nanu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209966357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209966357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-zake-mpya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209975807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209975807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_dawa-nasi-wali"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209984108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209984108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-nono-hizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209989880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209989875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-nono-hizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209997109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209997109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9f24a4e2-c240-4d15-a531-f6043c39ee4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-nono-hizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210007759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210007758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210011050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210011050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210012600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210012600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210016272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210016272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210017829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210017829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210021069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210021069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210022617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210022617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" NAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210026054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210026054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210027601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210027601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nalo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALO"," userResponse":" NALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210031132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210031132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nalo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210032683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210032683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210035974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210035974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210037522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210037522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210039914","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210039914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210041473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210041473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210044920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210044920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210046468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210046468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210050392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210050392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210051943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210051943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210055181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210055181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210057189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210057189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210057358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210057358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 116000d0-52e6-40f2-8f98-8ab5f98612e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210063789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210063789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 1ccd77b8-fdc1-451e-9437-8e32511f5736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210083122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210083122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 1ccd77b8-fdc1-451e-9437-8e32511f5736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210085846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210085844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 1ccd77b8-fdc1-451e-9437-8e32511f5736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210085984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210085984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 1ccd77b8-fdc1-451e-9437-8e32511f5736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210099128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210099128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6a3a09f5-b78a-431b-8454-470a16bdf460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_nayo-nani-pini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210116481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210116480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6a3a09f5-b78a-431b-8454-470a16bdf460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nami_lulu-hayo-nami"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nami"," userResponse":" nami"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210134634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210134634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6a3a09f5-b78a-431b-8454-470a16bdf460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nami_nami-adie-zile"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nami"," userResponse":" nami"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210134940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210134940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6a3a09f5-b78a-431b-8454-470a16bdf460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nami_nami-adie-zile"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210139612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210139611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6a3a09f5-b78a-431b-8454-470a16bdf460"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nami_nami-adie-zile"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210148897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210148897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210151900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210151900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210154771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210154771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210157881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210157881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210160983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210160983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210163927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210163926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210166387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210166387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210169433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210169433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210172325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210172325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210175251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210175250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.si.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210178881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210178880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210178946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210178946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210185615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210185614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 8b684a72-2848-4182-a06b-c3915c679a11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.si.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210200103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210200103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_dada-miwa-sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210209060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210209060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_mvua-hapa-siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210217650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210217650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siku_siku-kinu-boma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" siku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210226366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210226366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siku_siku-fupi-wako"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" siku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210241146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210241146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_mbao-sisa-wiki"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210251741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210251741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_miwa-sisi-bora"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210260279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210260279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sina_sina-mbao-pana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sina"," userResponse":" sina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210269075","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210269075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_siyo-wana-pini"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210282724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210282724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_simu_simu-isha-soko"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" simu"," userResponse":" isha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210292318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210292317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_simu_simu-isha-soko"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" simu"," userResponse":" simu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210302606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210302606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_simo_eupe-simo-opio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" simo"," userResponse":" simo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210308356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210308355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_simo_eupe-simo-opio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210314582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210314582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" f80a31e9-b381-486d-bc8b-46c71b98e744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_simo_eupe-simo-opio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210325866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210325865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210328200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210328200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210329753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210329753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210344692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210344692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210346270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210346270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210349484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210349484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210351042","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210351042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210354810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210354810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210356375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210356374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210359615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210359615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210361202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210361202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210369857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210369857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210371491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210371491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210378355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210378354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210379982","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210379981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210389838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210389838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210391469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210391469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210400292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210400292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210401955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210401955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210405891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210405891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210407901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210407901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210408066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210408066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" dabdf316-a291-48d9-8d5e-d1393c8a75e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210414690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210414690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210433236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210433234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210435892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210435892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210436003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210436003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210464936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210464935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210470420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210470420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210478786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210478785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3828d9ed-2ff2-42f5-a26f-429d5825b9e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210492036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210492036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210503005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210503005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210504180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210504180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210504647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210504647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210507708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210507708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210510074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210510074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210511670","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210511670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210515802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210515802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210517374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210517374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210521606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210521605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" START_SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210525232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210525232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210526831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210526830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210536401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210536400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210538056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210538055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210550112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210550111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210551759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210551759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210554509","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210554509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210556166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210556164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210569322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210569322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210570886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210570886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210574003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210574003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210576022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210576019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210576163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210576163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 3f300848-cc83-44b5-8fcb-31b4fe5b1196"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210586785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210586785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210591610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210591610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210599908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210599908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210605092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210605092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210610210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210610210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210616318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210616318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210620756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210620756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210626054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210626054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_10-11-12"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210631235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210631235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210638845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210638845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210744799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210744799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210751306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210751305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0102f509-7142-4dd9-a566-abbc5e0f853f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210773620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210773619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210785529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210785528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210787119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210787119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210791526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210791526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210793131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210793130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210796495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210796495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210798095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210798094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210801467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210801467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210803060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210803059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210805725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210805724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210807340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210807339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210810186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210810186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210811780","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210811780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210819193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210819192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210820839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210820839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210824177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210824177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210825770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210825769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210833256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210833256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210834859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210834859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210837998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210837998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.si.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210840013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210840012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210840095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210840095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210846041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210846041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea31308a-6516-4f89-acbc-607d799fba32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.si.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210870559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210870559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_babu-dudu-siyo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210880061","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210880061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_ndio-nina-sisi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210890035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210890035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_lako-sisi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210899152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210899152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sare-sisi-wake"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210908096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210908096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_goso-sisa-tisa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210922923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210922923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_kipi-zake-sisa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210931777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210931776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_pili-siyo-kale"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210952100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210952100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_wake-mkuu-siyo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" mkuu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210964972","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210964972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_wake-mkuu-siyo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210977845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210977845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sita_nusu-sita-embe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sita"," userResponse":" embe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549210989601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549210989601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sita_nusu-sita-embe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sita"," userResponse":" nusu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211000967","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211000967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sita_nusu-sita-embe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sita"," userResponse":" sita"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211040874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211040874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sisi-pesa-umwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211046615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211046615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sisi-pesa-umwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211073003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211073002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 685a4b2a-40a8-4fdc-b13b-dbc9609d0e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sisi-pesa-umwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211139212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211139212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_ndio-nina-sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211149939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211149939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_wake-mkuu-siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211161180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211161180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_babu-dudu-siyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211172274","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211172274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_lako-sisi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211180469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211180469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sare-sisi-wake"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sare"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211190434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211190433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sare-sisi-wake"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211199813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211199813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_sisi-pesa-umwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211208531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211208531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_goso-sisa-tisa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211217203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211217203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_kipi-zake-sisa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211227420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211227420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sita_nusu-sita-embe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sita"," userResponse":" sita"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211240469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211240469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_pili-siyo-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" siyo"," userResponse":" siyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.si.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211246203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211246203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_pili-siyo-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211252302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211252301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_pili-siyo-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211261660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211261660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 61426cb3-c97d-4d19-b173-66de10043c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.si.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_siyo_pili-siyo-kale"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211271609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211271609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211276554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211276554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211280757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211280757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211286979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211286979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211291636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211291636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211295778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211295778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211300423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211300423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211305112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211305112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211310899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211310899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_10-11-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211317559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211317559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211324580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211324580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211331660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211331659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 6e138581-f09d-4b12-91f2-16dd8b291b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211361626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211361626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211363236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211363236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211373353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211373352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211375869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211375869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211384070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211384070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211385666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211385666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211394220","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211394220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211395571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211395571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211403900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211403900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211410971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211410971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211417290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211417290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211421563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211421563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211427826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211427826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211435625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211435625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211442637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211442637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211452804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211452804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211459758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211459758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211466608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211466608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211469089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211469088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211474286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211474286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211481161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211481161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211487762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211487762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211498412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211498412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211504565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211504565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211511218","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211511218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211519342","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211519342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211521895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211521895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211527950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211527950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211537438","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211537438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211539353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211539353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211548308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211548308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211550627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211550627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211558808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211558808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211570181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211570181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211576617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211576617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211578980","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211578980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211590124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211590124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211596669","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211596668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" b3c95c53-b48e-4820-bf6f-ba0919074a42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211612251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211612251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211620401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211620401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-kile-jani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211628713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211628713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-nchi-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211637345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211637345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211650615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211650615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_lina-yale-tawi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211659192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211659192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211667256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211667256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211677474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211677474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211687394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211687394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211696916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211696915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-ubao-nanu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211707166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211707166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamu_tamu-wivu-yawe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamu"," userResponse":" tamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211715909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211715909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211720113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211720113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211725564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211725564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 571c639c-e7b1-4367-92af-703a3c646a1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211746639","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211746639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_taroli_tausi_tawi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211753270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211753270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tani_tani_tafadhali_tajiri"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211759929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211759928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tabia_tambarare_tangu_tabia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211766625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211766624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tamaa_taja_tamaa_tayari"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211773276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211773276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tamu_tamu_taa_taratibu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211780743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211780743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tamu_tamu_taa_taratibu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211787390","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211787390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tajiri_tajiri_tangu_taji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211794057","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211794057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tangu_tamu_tawi_tangu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211800699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211800699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" taa_taja_tangu_taa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211807343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211807343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tani_tabasamu_tani_tamu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211813973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211813973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" tabia_taya_taa_tabia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ta.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211827006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211827005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tabia_taya_taa_tabia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211839450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211839450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 0711f029-0417-4103-a50a-cacb3fcf717b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ta.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tabia_taya_taa_tabia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211854982","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211854982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211863884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211863884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ta.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211875966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211875965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211911473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211911473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ta.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211932265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211932265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211937554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211937553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ta.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211946273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211946273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 36f70ef2-06e0-43ac-90fc-b505b6450527"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211956017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211956017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211961448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211961447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211966392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211966392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211974820","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211974820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211982605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211982605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211988843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211988843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549211997441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549211997441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212002436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212002436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212008130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212008129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212012739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212012739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212016548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212016547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212025582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212025582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212029679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212029679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212040449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212040448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" ea5b92fe-008c-4433-b074-bbae2aee2ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212063458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212063458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212071782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212071782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212076009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212076009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212080038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212080038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212089378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212089378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212093585","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212093585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212102206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212102206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212106891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212106890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212111175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212111175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212119591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212119591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212124093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212124093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212128280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212128280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212132239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212132239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212135790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212135790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212144931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212144931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212150984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212150984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 32b393bf-5293-4c59-9fb9-3427fd90f6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212159741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212159741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212162553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212162553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waje"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJE"," userResponse":" WAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212165529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212165529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212177188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212177188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" WAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212180163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212180163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212183224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212183224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212189336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212189336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212192500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212192500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUA"," userResponse":" WAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212202941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212202941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212205940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212205940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212209327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212209327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212209440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212209440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212214187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212214187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212219888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212219888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212224130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212224130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212232076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212232076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212245979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212245979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 9ad543ef-f4fb-40ef-a56f-8e0669831063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.wa.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212262771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212262771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waje_hiki-humo-waje"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waje"," userResponse":" waje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212271786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212271786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_isha-moto-wako"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212281441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212281440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_kwao-wako-hivi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212290212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212290212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wake_wake-yawe-pale"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wake"," userResponse":" wake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212299756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212299756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wazo"," userResponse":" wazo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212309065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212309065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waje_humu-waje-njia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waje"," userResponse":" waje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212329203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212329203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wale_wale-papa-zile"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wale"," userResponse":" wale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212337949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212337949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wake_yote-ubao-wake"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wake"," userResponse":" wake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212346801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212346800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wavu_kuku-joto-wavu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wavu"," userResponse":" joto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212359523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212359522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wavu_kuku-joto-wavu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wavu"," userResponse":" wavu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212368086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212368085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wana"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212381214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212381214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wana"," userResponse":" wana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212387056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212387056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212393978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212393977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212400491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212400490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212405808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212405808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 991b27d0-e48d-4450-b29c-19b0d8e02542"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wana_yenu-wana-wewe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212420604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212420603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_isha-moto-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" moto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212434587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212434586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_isha-moto-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212442798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212442798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wake_yote-ubao-wake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wake"," userResponse":" yote"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212455993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212455993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wake_yote-ubao-wake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wake"," userResponse":" wake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212466247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212466247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_kwao-wako-hivi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212477345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212477345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wale_wale-papa-zile"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wale"," userResponse":" wale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212487192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212487192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wazo"," userResponse":" wazo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212539953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212539952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212545314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212545314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212553384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212553384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212558717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212558717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212567888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212567887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212574651","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212574651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212583523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212583523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212589574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212589574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.wa.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212597790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212597788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185833"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}